<form>
    <field>
        <id>general.enabled</id>
        <label>Enable</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Enable LCDproc service.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.loglevel</id>
        <label>Log Level</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Choose the level of detail the LCDproc daemon will write to the system log.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.comport</id>
        <label>COM port</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Set the com port LCDproc should use.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.size</id>
        <label>Display Size</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Set the display size LCDproc should use.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.driver</id>
        <label>Driver</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Select the LCD driver LCDproc should use. Some drivers will show additional settings.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.connection_type</id>
        <label>Connection Type</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Select the HD44780 connection type.</help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.mtxorb_type</id>
        <label>Display Type</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Select the Matrix Orbital display type.</help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.mtxorb_adjustable_backlight</id>
        <label>Has adjustable backlight</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Some firmware versions of Matrix Orbital and compatible modules do not support an adjustable backlight and only can switch the backlight on/off. If the LCD experiences randomly appearing block characters and the backlight cannot be switched on or off, uncheck the adjustable backlight option.</help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.mtxorb_backlight_color</id>
        <label>Background Color</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>LCD Background Color. Some Matrix Orbital compatible Adafruit controller boards have extended commands to set the background color. This works independently of the adjustable backlight checkbox. Leave at default if this feature is not supported.</help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.port_speed</id>
        <label>Port Speed</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Set the port speed. Caution: not all the driver or panels support all the speeds, leave "default" if unsure.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.refresh_frequency</id>
        <label>Refresh Frequency</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Set the duration for which each info screen will be displayed.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.outputleds</id>
        <label>Enable Output LEDs</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Enable the output LEDs present on some LCD panels. This feature is currently supported by the CFontzPacket driver only.</help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.controlmenu</id>
        <label>OPNsense control menu</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Enable the OPNsense control menu next to LCDproc's Options menu. Requires a display with buttons (e.g. CrystalFontz 635/735/835). Currently supports several basic functions including reboot and halt.</help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.brightness</id>
        <label>Brightness</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Set the brightness of the LCD panel. This option is not supported by all the LCD panels, leave "default" if unsure.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.contrast</id>
        <label>Contrast</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Set the contrast of the LCD panel. This option is not supported by all the LCD panels, leave "default" if unsure.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.backlight</id>
        <label>Backlight</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Set the backlight setting. If set to the default value, then the backlight setting of the display can be influenced by the clients. This option is not supported by all the LCD panels, leave "default" if unsure.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.offbrightness</id>
        <label>Off Brightness</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Set the off-brightness of the LCD panel. This value is used when the display is normally switched off in case LCDd is inactive. This option is not supported by all the LCD panels, leave "default" if unsure.</help>
    </field>
</form>
